Guide to the Douglas Crase and Frank Polach Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Douglas Crase papers, Series I
  - Correspondence
    - Incoming
      - Schulman, Grace, undated (Box 9)
      - Schultz, Susan, undated (Box 9)
      - Schultz, Prescott, undated (Box 9)
      - Schuyler, Helen, undated (Box 9)
      - Schuyler, James, undated (Box 9)
      - Schwabsky, Barry, undated (Box 9)
      - Schweighofer, William, undated (Box 9)
      - Seliger, Charles, undated (Box 9)
      - Seliger, Jonathan, undated (Box 9)
      - Sell, Michael, undated (Box 9)
      - Seneca, Joseph, undated (Box 9)
      - Sennett, Richard, undated (Box 9)
      - Shain, William, undated (Box 9)
      - Shapiro, Harvey, undated (Box 10)
      - Sharp, Jasper, undated (Box 10)
      - Shekerjian, Denise, undated (Box 10)
      - Shaw, Harley G., undated (Box 10)
      - Shaw, Robert, undated (Box 10)
      - Shetley, Vernon, undated (Box 10)
      - Shoub, Donald, undated (Box 10)
      - Shulgasser, Mark, undated (Box 10)
      - Schullenberger, Paul, undated (Box 10)
      - Sieber, Marilyn, undated (Box 10)
      - Siegel, Tema, undated (Box 10)
      - Sifton, Elizabeth, undated (Box 10)
      - Silverberg, Ira, undated (Box 10)
      - Silverberg, Mark, undated (Box 10)
      - Silvey, Ivy Chase (Schnell), undated (Box 10)
      - Simic, Charles, undated (Box 10)
      - Sinclair, Paul, undated (Box 10)
      - Singleton, D.W., undated (Box 10)
      - Sippell, Kelly, undated (Box 10)
      - Slattery, William, undated (Box 10)
      - Sloan, Benjamin, undated (Box 10)
      - Smith, Doug, undated (Box 10)
      - Smith, Gary, undated (Box 10)
      - Smith, Jordan, undated (Box 10)
      - Smith, Lee, undated (Box 10)
      - Smith, Thomas Spence, undated; 3 folders (Box 10)
      - Smith, Tony, undated (Box 10)
      - Sobiezek, Robert A., undated (Box 10)
      - Socolow, Daniel, undated (Box 10)
      - Sofield, David, undated (Box 10)
      - Solomon, Mike, undated (Box 10)
      - Sontag, Susan, undated (Box 10)
      - Sorel, Paul, undated (Box 10)
      - Sosland, Cynthia, undated (Box 10)
      - Sourian, Peter, undated (Box 10)
      - Staebler, Neil, undated (Box 10)
      - Staples, George, undated (Box 10)
      - Stark, Sheldon, undated (Box 10)
      - Starkoff, Robert, undated (Box 10)
      - Stebbins, Thomas, undated (Box 10)
      - Steel, Ronald, undated (Box 10)
      - Stein, Jean, undated (Box 10)
      - Steinberg, Barry, undated (Box 10)
      - Stephenson, Shelby, undated (Box 10)
      - Stewart, Gary, undated (Box 10)
      - Stimpson, Catharine, undated (Box 10)
      - Stolz, Mabel, undated (Box 10)
      - Storace, Patricia, undated (Box 10)
      - Stow, Julie (Garms), undated (Box 10)
      - Strachan, Pat, undated (Box 10)
      - Stromberg, Ragnar, undated (Box 10)
      - Stufano, Marco Polo, undated (Box 10)
      - Summers, Joseph, undated (Box 10)
      - SUNY Buffalo, undated (Box 10)
      - Suskewich, John, undated (Box 10)
      - Svoboda, Terese, undated (Box 10)
      - Swartz, Kelly, undated (Box 10)
      - Swetz Van Middhlar, C. Wolfram, undated (Box 10)
      - Tabler, Norman, undated (Box 10)
      - Tall, Deborah, undated (Box 10)
      - Tallman, Ray and Thelma, undated (Box 10)
      - Tart, Indrek, undated (Box 10)
      - Taylor, Bob, undated (Box 10)
      - Taylor, Harold, undated (Box 10)
      - Taylor, Justin, undated (Box 10)
      - Taylor, William, undated (Box 10)
      - Tessman, Gary, undated (Box 10)
      - Thiers, Barbara, undated (Box 10)
      - Thorp, Willard, undated (Box 10)
      - Tiehm, Arnold, undated (Box 10)
      - Tollerton, Thomas, undated (Box 10)
      - Towle, Tony, undated (Box 10)
      - Trinidad, David, undated (Box 10)
      - Triplett, Craig, undated (Box 10)
      - Tucker, Martin, undated (Box 10)
      - Tulinsky, Alexander, undated (Box 10)
      - Turner, Billie, undated (Box 10)
      - Turner, Frederick, undated (Box 10)
      - Turner, Matt, undated (Box 10)
      - Turner, Stacie, undated (Box 10)
      - Twichell, Evelyn, undated (Box 10)
      - Twichell, Richard, undated (Box 10)
      - Tyminski, Robert, undated (Box 10)
      - Vanden Heuvel, Katrina, No date (Box 10)
      - Van Goethem, Nancy, No date (Box 10)
      - Van Hulzen, Todd, No date (Box 10)
      - Van Vactor, David, No date (Box 10)
      - Varnedoe, Kirk, No date (Box 10)
      - Veitch, Laurel, No date (Box 10)
      - Vidal, Gore, No date (Box 10)
      - Vendler, Helen, No date (Box 10)
      - Virtue, Veronica, No date (Box 10)
      - Vitalgino, John, No date (Box 10)
      - Vogelsang, Arthur, No date (Box 10)
      - Voigt, Ellen Bryant, No date (Box 10)
      - Wagner, Alex, No date (Box 10)
      - Wagoner, David, No date (Box 10)
      - Walker, Brian, No date; 7 folders (Box 11)
      - Wallace, Don and Mindy Pennybacker, No date (Box 11)
      - Walmsley, Mary Edith (Fuller), No date (Box 11)
      - Walsh, James, No date (Box 11)
      - Wasserman, Rosanne, No date (Box 11)
      - Watkins, Lynda, No date (Box 11)
      - Weiner, Joy, No date (Box 11)
      - Weiss, Fae, No date (Box 11)
      - Welish, Marjorie, No date; 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Wells, Andrea, No date (Box 11)
      - Wells, John, No date (Box 11)
      - Welsh, Stanley, No date (Box 11)
      - Wheeler, Susan, No date (Box 11)
      - Whitaker, Rick, No date; 2 folders (Box 11)
      - White, Edmund, No date (Box 11)
      - Whiteside, Thomas, No date (Box 11)
      - Whiting (cf. Freund, Bristol, Rosenheim), No date (Box 11)
      - Whitton, B.A., No date (Box 11)
      - Wickert, Max, No date (Box 11)
      - Wilhelm, Bea, No date (Box 11)
      - Wilkin, Karen, No date (Box 11)
      - Williams, G. Mennen, No date (Box 11)
      - Williams, Jonathan, No date (Box 11)
      - Wilshinsky, Andrew, No date (Box 11)
      - Wilson, Kenneth Jay, No date (Box 11)
      - Wilson, William S., No date (Box 11)
      - Winkfield, Trevor, No date; 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Winnick, Steven and Sandy, No date (Box 11)
      - Winterrowd, Wayne, No date (Box 11)
      - Wipprecht, Wendy, No date (Box 11)
      - Wise, Kelly, No date (Box 11)
      - Wojahn, David, No date (Box 11)
      - Wojciechowski, Martin, No date (Box 11)
      - Wolf, Leslie, No date (Box 11)
      - Worklan, Mary Ann, No date (Box 11)
      - Workman, Judy (Holly), No date (Box 11)
      - Worthington, Rain, No date (Box 11)
      - Wright, Jay, No date (Box 11)
      - Wright, Rita, No date (Box 11)
      - Yamaguchi, Yoji, No date (Box 11)
      - Yau, John, No date (Box 11)
      - Yenser, Stephen, No date (Box 11)
      - Zapruder, Matthew, No date (Box 11)
      - Zavatsky, Bill, No date (Box 11)
      - Zelinsky, Mary O'Brien, No date (Box 11)
      - Zona, Scott, No date (Box 11)
    - Outgoing, 1964-1996; 8 folders (Box 12)
  - Writings
    - Prose
      - Various, 1968-1984 (Box 13)
        Includes: Dems (Michigan Democrats) in Disarray, 1968 (The Nation); New Politics, 1968, p.461 (The Nation); Dems (Democrats) Confront (1970), 1969, p.598 (The Nation); NDC Ad ("The Non-Election"), 1968 (The Michigan Daily); Manley Armstrong, 1968; Early mss, 1986-1971? (Journalism 710); NDC press release, written by Crase (Douglas), 1969; NDC Article ("A New Democratic Coalition), 1969 (NY Times, Arnie Kaufman); Political Commission Reform Report (Michigan Democratic Party), 1969; Levin (Sander) campaign memo, DC, 1969 ("I'm Damn Encouraged"); Levin (Sander) announcement, 1970; Kent State speech, DC, 1970; Doner (W.B. & Co.), Wrigley Anti-Pollution Bulletin, 1971; The Narrows (ideas); Pontiac (timeline, 1720-1769); New Medievalism (note); "The Loves of Martin" (draft & notes); "Percy Jones Jackson" (draft & notes); "The Huron Event" (First North American Serial Rights); In Face of Ellen (original); Bridge Proposal, 1973 (Eastman Kodak Co.); "Leftover Landscape" (drafts 1-3); American Landscapes (magazines, photos); Landscape notes; JA (John Ashbery) Rochester Library award, 4/22/1977; Southampton College, 1976 (notes for talk); LLE (Laboratory for Laser Energetics) Dedication, 10/17/1978; "The Prophetic Ashbery," annotated; "The Prophetic Ashbery," October 1978, original; JA (John Ashbery) draft ("The Commonwealth of John Ashbery"); JA (John Ashbery) working draft; JA (John Ashbery) notes; Family Landscape (Dash (Robert) film), 1980 (Chesebrough-Pond's); Fallon (Walter)—Chandler(Colby): annual meeting (1980, Kodak); IPD research (1980); Hirschl & Adler (Galleries), Continental American Landscape, 1981; Annual meeting, 5/6/1981, Ft.Collins, CO; American Civil Meter, Epoch, 1983 ("Once the Sole Province"); Dead Tech—Metro Corridor, Art & Antiques (magazine), 12/09/82; Dead Tech (notes)
      - Various, 1966-1995 (Box 14)
        Includes: Ashbery (John), A Wave, The Nation, 7/21/1984; Contemporary Authors, 1985; Schuyler (James), A Few Days, The Nation, Nov/1985; Niedecker (Lorine), Academy of American Poets, 1985; Niedecker (Lorine) Review, The Nation, March 1986; Bradley (George) FTN, 1986 (Terms To Be Met review); Bradley (George) research 1986; Edward Abbey Ltr, 1986; Moore (Marianne) FTN, 1986 (complete prose); Moore (Marianne) research, 1986; Moore (Marianne); Moore (Marianne): Drafts, 1986; Lewis (Leon) letter re: Moore (Marianne); Emerson (Ralph Waldo) txt, book version, 12/03/87; Emerson (Ralph Waldo) review, Boulevard version, 11/30/87; Emerson (Ralph Waldo) PDM (podium copy), 01/12/87; Emerson (Ralph Waldo) research, 1986-87; Poirier (Richard) FTN, 1987 (Emersonian Reflections); Poirier (Richard) research 1987; Vintage Emerson (Ralph Waldo), 1/1/89 (Emerson's Essays); Schuyler (James, Jimmy) Ballade, 1989; Emerson (Ralph Waldo)—Woodward (C. Vann) letter, 4/15/90, 5/14/90; Gerstler (Amy) review, 1990; Journal excerpt, Seneca Review, 1991; Niedecker (Lorine), Penberthy (Jenny) book version (4/25/95); Niedecker (Lorine) & Evolutional Sublime, 1991; Niedecker (Lorine) reserach; Niedecker (Lorine), Lake Superior Notes, 1966; Niedecker (Lorine), Correspondence & bio. material; Schuyler (James, Jimmy) memorial, 1992; Pyrrhic Measure, 1992 (The Pyrrhic Measure of American Poetry); Schuyler (James, Jimmy) collect'd, 1993; Pyrrhic Life, 1993 (The Pyrrhic Life of Poems); Lauterbach (Ann), intro at 92nd st. Y
      - Various, 1991-2013 (Box 15)
        Includes: Niedecker (Lorine), 1991 ("Niedecker and the Evolutional Sublime," etc Amerifil. BAS; "The Art and Romance of Dwight Ripley" (unpublished work, 2001); "The Art of Dwight Ripley," 05/10/2000 (Rupert version); "Dwight" draft, 12/7/02 (Trevor version); "Both" layout design; Illustrations (draft list for "Both"); Bibliography (selected, for "Both"); "Both" reading, Monkey Temple Bar, 6/8/2004 (introductory notes); Poets House show in The New Yorker (3/20/2006); Poets House show, expenses, 2005; Poets House exhibit, 2006 (Ripley & Barneby: Unlikely Angel); Esopus II, 2008; Rosenthal (Deborah) card, 2008; Schiavo (Michael) foreword, 2008 ("The Mad Song"); Esopus Space review, 2009 (Dwight Ripley: Travel Posters); Esopus Space, 2009 (Dwight Ripley: Travel Posters); NY School seminar, Princeton 2010 (ENG 563: History—Evol. of the NY School); Chronology, Painters & Poets (Tibor de Nagy: The Remaking of the Avant-Garde); Bibliography, Painters & Poets; "Hidden History" epigraphs ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"; "Elsewhere" by Roland Pease, excerpt; "Hidden History" drafts ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); "Hidden History" outline ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); "Hidden History" note out-takes ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); "Hidden History" notes ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); Painters & Poets (Tibor de Nagy) reviews; "Hidden History," annotated ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); "Hidden History" drafts notebook ("A Hidden History of the Avant-Garde"); Painters & Poets, New School, 1/31/2011 (Tibor de Nagy and the NY School Poets); Ripley (Dwight), extended chronology, 2012; Ripley (Dwight), Tibor (de Nagy Gallery) 2012 show; Ripler (Dwight) show, Tibor (de Nagy Gallery) 2012, catalog drafts; Jaffe (Michelle), 2012; Jaffe (Michelle), research; Jaffe (Michelle), correspondence
    - Both
      - Manuscripts, drafts, research materials, correspondence, reviews and other related items. Including Crase college notebooks., 1960s-2004 (Box 16)
        Manuscripts, drafts, research materials, correspondence, reviews and other related items. Including Crase college notebooks.
      - Card Files, 1908-1965 (Box 17)
      - Card Files, 1908-1965 (Box 18)
      - Manuscripts, drafts, research materials, correspondence, reviews and other related items., 2000-2007 (Box 19)
        Contains material from The Art and Romance of Dwight Ripley, Ruperti Imagines and Both.
      - Manuscripts, drafts, research materials, correspondence, reviews and other related items., 2003, undated (Box 20)
        Contains material, drafts, and galleys from Both, as well as assorted magazines and publications.
      - Manuscripts, drafts, research materials, correspondence, reviews and other related items., 2005 (Box 21)
        1st pass, 2nd pass, index drafts, manuscript.
    - Poetry
      - Revisionist and Other Poems, 1979 (Box 22)
        Including manuscripts and record of submissions (index card box)
    - Journals and notebooks
      - Typed, printed journals, 1967-2012 (Box 23)
      - Manuscript journals and notes, 1974-1990 (Box 24)
        Includes: Handwritten journals 1977–1984 (black, red spine and corners); 1984–1989 (black, red spine and corners); 1989–1990 (black, rip on cover); Pocket Journals—Notebooks 1974 (white, "Weekly Pocket Diary"); 1975 (blue, "the Spiral notebook"); 1975 (yellowed, "Personal Pocket Diary"); 1976–? (blue, "the Spiral notebook"); 1976 (black, "Personal Pocket Diary"); 1977 (white, "Week at a Glance"); 1978 (white, "Personal Pocket Diary"); 1978 (black, "Week at a Glance"); 1983 (yellow, "handi notes," date on cover may be inaccurate); 1984 (yellow, "handi notes," includes entry from 1981); n.d. (teal, "memo book"); Assorted Early Notes—1968–1972 (folder); Pyrrhic notes—1992 (3-ring binder); Poets House Panel—2006 (printed notes); Vietnam & Poetry—n.d. (folder); Porter—n.d. (3-ring binder); Stack slips (call slips)—n.d.; Notes—n.d. (index cards)
    - Assorted material
      - Kodak speeches, 1980-1983 (Box 25)
      - Publications by Douglas Crase, 1970-1999 (Box 26)
        magazine, catalogs, anthologies, books.
      - Kodak speeches, 1973-1979 (Box 27)
      - Juvenilia and College material, 1950-1969 (Box 28)
      - Mixed material, 1960-2009 (Box 29)
        Publications by Douglas Crase (magazine, catalogs, anthologies, books, assorted [calandars])
      - College politics, 1960-1979 (Box 30)
      - Kodak sales films, 1980-1989 (Box 83)
        16 mm film.
      - Kodak sales films, 1980-1989 (Box 84 (Oversize))
  - Writings and publications of others
    - Various authors, 1970-2010 (Box 31)
      Marjorie Welish, John Ash, John Koethe, George Bradley and Charles North among others, all dedicated or given to Douglas and Frank as a couple, or Douglas. The manuscripts have been compiled in a notebook by Douglas.; Winkfield, Trevor (folder) Approx. 15 assorted items, including catalogs and articles.; Rosenthal, Deborah (folder) Approx. 30 items, including: articles, exhibit ads.; MacArthur, Marit Poems, mss., 2011.; Schmall, Jeremy "American Mud," ms., 2010.; Schmall, Jeremy "Open Correspondence From the Senator, Vol.1," 2008.; Kaufman, Arnold S. (folder) Arnold Kaufman, University of Michigan philosophy professor, advisor to SDS and advocate for the Democratic Party's move to the left. He was a friend and mentor to Douglas Crase.; Approx. 4 items, including political articles. Bibbins, Mark "The Anxiety of Coincidence," printout, 2012. "The Mary and Laurance S. Rockefeller Chapel of Hope and Remembrance at the Healthcare Chaplaincy" (brochure).; Dash, Robert (folder) Approx. 10 assorted items, including catalogs, ads.; Park, Darragh (small box) Approx. 5 assorted items, including catalogs, postcard, "Paintings" printout.; Sanders, Tony "Imperative," ms.; Fuller, Margaret "Loveloft." ms.; Welish, Marjorie "Jasper's Patterns," printout, 1990.; Welish, Marjorie "Jasper's Patterns" (including photo printouts of Jasper pieces), ms.; Welish, Marjorie (folder) Approx. 20 assorted items, including catalogs, articles, notes, interviews.; Welish, Marjorie "The Annotated "Here" and Selected Poems," ms.; Welish, Marjorie "Casting Sequences," ms.; Welish, Marjorie "Nightly Arbitrariness," ms.; Perl, Jed "Connoly's Unquiet" and "Vagrant Thoughts About Quality" (printouts).; Perl, Jed (folder) Approx. 10 assorted items including articles. Perl, Jed "Antoine's Alphabet," ms.; Wadsworth, Bill "Genius as Pariah" and "Six Poems by George Barker" (printouts).; Delatolas, Iannis "Alice in a Football Field," + photo, 2004.
    - Various authors, 1970-2010 (Box 32)
      Koethe, John (folder) Approx. 10 assorted items, including essays, manuscripts.; Koch, Kenneth (folder) "Angelica," ms.; Smith, Thomas Spence "Strong Interaction," ms.; Earl, Martin (folder) Poems, mss.; Walker, Brian (folder) Approx. 15 assorted items, including essays, notes, printouts.; Smith, Thomas Spence "Instability and Complexity in Interaction Systems: Some Observations on Forms of Structuration," ms., June 1993.; Bradley, George (folder) Approx. 4 assorted items, including notes, printouts.; Haaren, Peter "Pharmacy," ms.; Schwabsky, Barry (folder) Approx. 5 assorted items, including: ms., articles.; Smith, Thomas Spence (folder) Approx. 7 assorted items, including: essays, ms., articles.; Smith, Thomas Spence and Paul Westcott (folder) "Interpreting the Effects of Distance on the Migration of Crime in Urban Areas."; Smith, Thomas Spence (folder) "Aestheticism and Social Structure: Style and Social Network in the Dandy Life."; Smith, Tony (folder) Dissertation chapts. 1–3, ms.; Johnson, Tom (folder) Approx. 10 assorted items, including: poetry mss., articles, printouts.; Wisconsin Court of Appeals Court cases.; Gutierrez, Ramon "When Padre Jesus Came, the Corn Mothers Went Away..." and article, "Honor Ideology, Marriage Negotiation, and Class-Gender Domination in New Mexico..." ms.; Koethe, John "The Continuity of Wittgenstein's Thought," ms.
    - Various authors, 1970-2010 (Box 33)
      Kernan, Nathan "Past=Past: Some Notes on James Schuyler's 'Salute'" ms. Kernan, Nathan "Introduction" (on James Schuyler), ms.,; Koethe, John "The Menomonee Valley," ms. Koethe, John "Sally's Hair," ms. Koethe, John and Marjorie Welish Correspondences ("electronic tete-a-tete"). Koethe, John (folder) Approx. 20 assorted items, including articles, reviews, letters, printouts. Koethe, John (8 envelopes) Assorted poetry mss. (some with ALS). Koethe, John (1 folder with 10 envelopes). Assorted poetry mss. (some with ALS). Koethe, John The Constructor (with notes and corrections by Douglas Crase), ms. Koethe, John "The Great Gatsby," ms. Koethe, John "Ninety-Fifth Street," ms. Koethe, John "The Distinguished Thing," ms. Koethe, John Ninety-Fifth Street (#2), ms. Koethe, John The Late Wisconsin Spring, ms. (+ 1 ALS).; Lehman, David From The Last Avant-Garde, Chapt. 4—"John Ashbery: The Picture of Little J.A. in a Prospect of Flowers," ms.; Meyer, Steven (envelope) Assorted including material on "Gertrude Stein @ the Millennium."; Kinzie, Mary Ghost Ship, 1996, proof.; Karpeles, Eric On Elizabeth Bishop exhibition (Tibor de Nagy) printout.; Schiavo, Michael The Desired Country, ms. (+ e-mail printouts).; Mitchell, Susan (folder) Erotikon, ms.; Fulton, Alice Sensual Math, uncorrected proof.; Joseph, Lawrence Into It, publisher's proof.; Joseph, Lawrence Into It, ms. Joseph, Lawrence "A Year after the Acquittal in the Impeachment Trial," photocopy. Joseph, Lawrence "The Music Is," photocopy.; Hadas, Rachel (envelope) Approx. 5 assorted items, including: ACS, offprints of poems (5).; Haaren, Peter Pharmacy (revised), ms., (+ TLS). Haaren, Peter "Autumnal Mobile," ms., (+ ALS).; Allardt, Linda "The Names of the Survivors," ms.
    - James Schuyler and John Ashbery
      - James Schuyler and John Ashbery, 1980-1990 (Box 34)
        Douglas Crase. "A Voice like the Day." Corrected mss. Essay on James Schuyler published in Poetry 163, no. 4 (January 1994); James Schuyler. The Morning of the Poem, 1980. Bound uncorrected page proof with penciled annotations by Crase; James Schuyler. The Morning of the Poem, 1980. Schuyler has written and inscribed the four-page poem "For Frank" on the book's front end papers, March 19, 1980. The book includes the poem "Dining Out with Doug and Frank (for Frank Polach); James Schuyler. The Morning of the Poem, 1980. Photocopy of manuscript with assorted correspondence regarding which poems were to be included; The "Queen Anne" cherry issue Frank to di Capra. Research done by Frank Polach for a Schuyler poem; Reviews of The Morning of the Poem including Charles North review from L=A=N=G=U=A=G=E with note from North; John Ashbery manuscripts and proofs (some with notes by Crase). Including A Wave, Knocking Around (published as As We Know), Houseboat Days; Assorted reviews and publications.
  - Other papers
    - "Audio visual materials", 1970-2010 (Box 35)
    - Crase family genealogy archive (Box 36)
      Edith Fuller's senior Latin project on Ralph Waldo Emerson, 1912; Fuller was Douglas Crase's grandmother. She raised him until the age of 5 or 6 and played a pivotal role in his life.; Six Generations Mother and Daughter; Matrimonial history prepared by Douglas for his parents' 50th wedding anniversary.; Letters of David Fuller, ca. 1850s; Letters from Douglas's great great grandfather David Fuller (a wood plane maker from rural Maine).; Photographs (daguerreotypes?) (4); Erastus Fuller, 1830–1915; David Fuller, 1795–1871; Mary Drew Fuller, 1799–1877; David H. Fuller, 1824–1854; Mary E. (Fuller) Walmsley, 1885–1969. Fuller family history, approx. 28 pp.; Handwritten "To my dear Grand Children."; Jennie A. Long. Record of the Belden Family: From the First Family Who Came to America 1641 Handwritten composition book. Appears to have written in the 1920s.; Assorted items related to the family genealogy.
    - Other material, 1960-2010 (Box 37)
      Frank Polach diplomas and certificates; Darragh Park. Pencil drawing of view from James Schuyler's window at Chelsea Hotel. In frame and inscribed to Douglas from Park, November 1995. The drawing was used for the cover of James Schuyler and Darragh Park's Two Journals (Tibor de Nagy Editions, 1995). Douglas wrote in the book's introduction: "This is the view out Jimmy Schuyler's window onto 23rd Street—'a street that doesn't have much going for it,' if I remember Jimmy's description aright... Darragh gave me this drawing and I have it in my studio here in Pennsylvania so I can always share Jimmy's view—this much at least." George Bradley. "Gathered from the Tempest," 2004. Signed letterpress broadside.; National Book Critics Circle Nomination for The Revisionist, 1981, other certificates, and "first poetry acceptances" (in plastic folder); Douglas Crase. "Theme Park," Numbered 9 of 100 and signed letterpress broadside.; Center for Book Arts, June 8, 2011.; Douglas Crase MacArthur Fellow certificate, 1987–1992; Douglas Crase Princeton diploma, 1966. and others.
    - Oversize, 1970-2010 (Box 38 (Oversize))
      Oversize photos- Robert Dash painting, 1979; Marilyn (Douglas Crase ex-wife), 1964; Doug and Frank at Bob's, 1991; Douglas and Frank's wedding, 2011; Founders' Monument, Harford, 2011. The New York Times, May 4, 1976 Issue announcing Pulitzer prizes for the year. Autographed by John Ashbery. Other material.
    - Darragh Park, pencil drawing in frame., 1995 (Box 39 (Art))